Meet Carl. His wife. & the Love of his Life.
Three Night Stand is a romance, comedy, drama film directed by Pat Kiely.
A man's plans for a romantic weekend go awry when he learns that his ex-girlfriend, whom he
still secretly loves, manages the ski lodge where he and his wife are staying.
Carl, played by Sam Huntington.
Sue, played by Meaghan Rath.
Robyn, played by Emmanuelle Chriqui.
Stacey, played by Reagan Pasternak.
Doug, played by Jonathan Cherry.
Aaron Berg, played by Dan Beirne.
Stand by Me Doraemon (Japanese: STAND BY ME ドラえもん, Hepburn: Sutando Bai Mī Doraemon) is a 2014 Japanese animated science
fiction comedy-drama film based on the Doraemon manga series and directed by Ryūichi Yagi and Takashi Yamazaki.
It was released on 8 August 2014.
It is the highest-grossing film of the Doraemon franchise.
Entertainment premiered an English-dubbed version of the film at the
Tokyo International Film Festival on 24 October 2014.
Stand by Me Doraemon was commercially successful in Japan.
It was number one on the box office charts for five consecutive weeks and was the second highest-grossing
animated film of 2014 in Japan, with a box office total of $183.4 million, behind Disney's Frozen.
In February 2015, the film won the Japan Academy Prize for
Animation of the Year at the 38th Japan Academy Prize.
A sequel was released on 20 November 2020 in Japan.
The film is primarily based on the first chapter of the manga "All the Way From the Future", the 1973 chapter "Mountain Rescue", the 1980 chapter "Goodbye Shizuka", the 1984 chapter "Imprinting
Shizuka", the 1998 short film "Doraemon Comes Back" and the 1999 short film "Doraemon: Nobita's Night Before a Wedding", though several other chapters are briefly brought up as well.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.